{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Seamless Gutter Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40071/":{"taskOID":40071,"originalTaskOID":40071,"setID":393,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":943,"questionDisplayText":"Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which problems need repair.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2890,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gutter is sagging or broken loose","answerDisplayText":"Gutter is sagging or broken loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6885,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water not draining due to improper slope","answerDisplayText":"Water not draining due to improper slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3507,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Leaking from seams","answerDisplayText":"Leaking from seams","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2067,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Downspout or gutter is clogged, disconnected or broken","answerDisplayText":"Downspout or gutter is clogged, disconnected or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2889,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Gutter is dented","answerDisplayText":"Gutter is dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3027,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hole in gutter","answerDisplayText":"Hole in gutter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5427,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Rotted gutter material","answerDisplayText":"Rotted gutter material","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":642,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add or move downspout","answerDisplayText":"Add or move downspout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":943,"questionDisplayText":"Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which problems need repair.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2890,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gutter is sagging or broken loose","answerDisplayText":"Gutter is sagging or broken loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6885,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water not draining due to improper slope","answerDisplayText":"Water not draining due to improper slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3507,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Leaking from seams","answerDisplayText":"Leaking from seams","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2067,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Downspout or gutter is clogged, disconnected or broken","answerDisplayText":"Downspout or gutter is clogged, disconnected or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2889,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Gutter is dented","answerDisplayText":"Gutter is dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3027,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hole in gutter","answerDisplayText":"Hole in gutter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5427,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Rotted gutter material","answerDisplayText":"Rotted gutter material","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":642,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add or move downspout","answerDisplayText":"Add or move downspout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2890,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gutter is sagging or broken loose","answerDisplayText":"Gutter is sagging or broken loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6885,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water not draining due to improper slope","answerDisplayText":"Water not draining due to improper slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3507,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Leaking from seams","answerDisplayText":"Leaking from seams","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2067,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Downspout or gutter is clogged, disconnected or broken","answerDisplayText":"Downspout or gutter is clogged, disconnected or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2889,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Gutter is dented","answerDisplayText":"Gutter is dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3027,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hole in gutter","answerDisplayText":"Hole in gutter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5427,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Rotted gutter material","answerDisplayText":"Rotted gutter material","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":642,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add or move downspout","answerDisplayText":"Add or move downspout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376531155pwspr014F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40071/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40071,"taskName":"Seamless Metal Gutters - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair or Replace Section of Seamless Metal Gutters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Seamless Gutter Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":112,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Seamless Metal Gutters copper cover","textMessagingName":"Repr Alum Gutter","rolloverLongDesc":"Gutter installers form continuous, seamless metal gutters to fit site-measured field dimensions \u0026 individual roof profiles.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes \"seamless\" gutters \u0026 downspouts.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Replace Section of Seamless Metal Gutters .  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Seamless Gutter Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Metal \u0026 Aluminum Gutter Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Seamless Metal Gutter Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Seamless Metal Gutters - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Seamless Gutter Project","urlName":"Seamless-Metal-Gutters-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Seamless Gutter Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Seamless,Metal,Gutters,copper,cover,vinyl,downspouts,rain,guard,drainspouts,aluminum","emcCategoryOid":-12038,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":393,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}